

KASHISH MAHTANI

Copy & Content Writer

About Me

With over 8.5 years of experience, I've developed copy and content for both digital and offline channels such as social media, paid media, OOH, radio, TV & more. This includes 1.5 years as a copy supervisor, leading a team of copywriters and managing campaigns for national and global brands, across industries.



+91 9051238131



kashishmahtani01@gmail.com



Pune

EXPERTISE

- Management Skills
- Creative Thinking
- Digital Marketing
- Negotiation
- Critical Thinking
- Leadership

EXPERIENCE

Amura Marketing Technologies - Copy Supervisor Nov 2022 - Present

Supervised senior copywriters while leading copywriting for clients such as Cummins India, Business Gateways International, Apptad, Power Cloud Consultancy, Apollo Spectra, Enparadigm and more.

upGrowth Digital - Senior Copywriter Sept 2020 - Nov 2022

Developed impactful content for marketing campaigns, websites, newsletters, blogs, articles, video scripts and other promotional materials deAsra Foundation, Women Entrepreneurship Platform - NITI Aayog and more.

Bright Brain Marketing Technologies - Senior Copywriter Oct 2018 - Nov 2019

Produced ATL and BTL content such as hoardings, standees, articles, video scripts, infographics, bus branding, leaflets, etc. while aligning with brand voice and objectives. Clients included Force Motors Ltd, ANP Corp, Paranjape Schemes.

Amura Marketing Technologies - Copy Executive Feb 2016 - April 2018

Produced copy and content for Google ads, social media, websites, landing pages, articles, newsletters, radio jingles/ads, hoardings, leaflets. site branding, etc. Clients included Oberoi Realty, Shapoorji Pallonji, Goel Ganga Developments, Gera Developers, VTP Realty and more.

LANGUAGE

- English
- Hindi
- Bengali
- Punjabi

EXPERIENCE

Marketing Internship

- Lowe Lintas, Kolkata | May June 2015
- 93.5 Red FM, Kolkata | Dec 2013 Jan 2014

Social Media Influencer & Blogger 2013 - Present

Content creation for F&B and lifestyle brands

CERTIFICATIONS

- Social Media Certified HubSpot Academy - 2021
- Content Marketing Certified -HubSpot Academy - 2020
- Inbound Marketing Certified -HubSpot Academy - 2020

EDUCATION

- M.A in Journalism & Mass Communication University of Calcutta 2013-2015
- Post-Graduate Diploma in Integrated Marketing Communications

St. Xavier's College, Kolkata 2014-2015

• B.Com (Hons)

J.D Birla Institute, Jadavpur University, Kolkata 2009-2012

I hereby declare, all the above information provided is true to my knowledge